First Last

Web Developer

Web Developer with five years of experience managing multiple website and web application design projects. Adept at developing creative and functional designs, web page layouts, color schemes, and infrastructure to maintain a cohesive website consistent with clients' needs.

San Francisco, CA 12345 +1 234 567-890 first.last@resumeworded.com linkedin.com/in/resumeworded

EXPERIENCE

Resume Worded, New York, NY

Web Developer

January 2020 - Present

- Revamped web application security applications, minimizing hacker attacks from 2% to 0.03%.
- Designed and developed a user-friendly website, including an optimized check-out page that increased user clicks, and subsequently customer purchases by 15%.
- Trained over 30 staff members in internal web functions.
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that improved functionality and efficiency by 25%.

Growthsi, Remote

Web Design Specialist

July 2016 - January 2020

- Managed 15+ web design projects from start to finish using HTML5,
 JavaScript, and CSS3 with 100% client satisfaction.
- Designed and allocated interactive flyers and ads on the site for upcoming promotions and events, increasing site visits by 25%.
- Redesigned 3 websites for top brands using a content management system, driving UX results by 20% and customer retention rate by 10%.

Resume Worded, Boston, MA

Web Designer

January 2012 - June 2016

- Managed all aspects of professional website design focusing on overall site navigation and information architecture for 30+ commercial and personal websites.
- Created 5+ responsive websites and custom graphic sets for clients, achieving a 100% client satisfaction rate.
- Delivered a wide range of web services to include web editing, multimedia animation, virtual postcards, flash sites, and interface design.

SKILLS

Critical Thinking
Programming
Operations Analysis
Visual Basic
XML / HTML
Oracle / .NET / CSS
Dreamweaver
WordPress

EDUCATION

Resume Worded University

Bachelor of Web Development January 2012

New York, NY

- Awards: Resume Worded Web Design Fellow (only 3 awarded to class), Dean's List 2012 (Top 10%)
- Completed one-year study abroad with Singapore University

OTHER

- Volunteer 20 hours/month at the ABC foundation, leading online projects
- PMP-certified (2020)